http://carolinabarbecue.com/privacy-notice/

Loading... Please wait...
Privacy Notice
Chandler Foods, Inc. has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our clients' privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website (http://www.carolinabarbecue.com). Our site's registration form requires users to provide contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, phone number). The information gathered is used to contact the visitor when necessary but is never shared with any party outside of Chandler Foods, Inc.
Information Automatically Logged: We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and to gather broad demographic information. This provides information on which parts of the site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session is tracked, but the user remains anonymous.
Cookies: Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ads repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.
Advertisers: We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information:  We do collect any personal information on this web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties.  The information collected is used by the credit card company in processing orders.
External Links: This site contains links to other sites. Chandler Foods, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums: This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and that you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security: This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Children's Guidelines:We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:
We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:
Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.
Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes.
We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.
New Products
Beef Barbecue with Tomato Sauce
$39.00
Pulled Chicken with Barbecue Sauce
$39.00
All Meat Hotdog Chili
$23.50
Premium Pork Barbecue with Tomato Based Sauce
Your Name:
Your Email:
Copyright 2020 Carolina Barbecue.
Sitemap |
Shopping Cart Software by BigCommerce
